Shrikant Joshi

QA Engineer

shrikantjoshi619@gmail.com 🔀

8839453695

indore, India

1.1......

India

linkedin.com/in/shrikant-joshi-b12726189 in

Senior QA Engineer with over 6 years of professional experience in all stages of Software QA, including manual and some automated testing. Thorough knowledge of SDLC, testing approaches and techniques including Functional, Mobile app, System, Web app and Regression tests. Enthusiastic entry level Scrum Master, worked in agile environment as a QA engineer for 6 years. Worked on two Scrum teams and filled in as Scrum Master on several occasions. Proven history of successful work with cross-functional teams.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Senior QA Engineer

Infobens

02/2021 - Present

Indore, India

- Responsibility
- Implementing testing procedures and overseeing the QA process.
- Leading the QA team in designing QA test procedures.
- Troubleshooting quality issues and modifying test procedures.

QA Manual Engineer

YASH Technologies

10/2016 - 01/2021 Indore, India

- Responsibility
- Meeting with the software/product designers to determine quality assurance parameters.
- Leading the QA team in designing QA test procedures.
- Implementing testing procedures and overseeing the QA process.

QA Manual Engineer

Biz4solutions

09/2015 - 09/2016 Pune, India

- Responsibility
- Create tests to identify software problems.
- Analyze bugs and errors found during tests.
- Works together with the software developer to enhance and improve programs.

QA Manual Engineer

KPIT

06/2014 - 12/2014

Pune, India

- Responsibility
- Test current products and identifying deficiencies.
- Plan, create and manage the overall Quality Planning strategy.
- Identify quality assurance process bottleneck and suggest actions for improvement.

SKILLS



EDUCATION

O Bachelor of Engineering

REPV, Bhopal, India

08/2008 - 06/2012

. RE

- Information Technology

CERTIFICATES

Salesforce Certified Administrator (02/2021 - Present)

Conference/Issuer of the certificate

 Certification - Administrator. Candidates should possess broad knowledge of customizing Salesforce, regularly configuring the platform, managing users, and looking for ways to get even more out of its features and capabilities

Certified Scrum Master (01/2019 - Present)

Description

 The scrum master is responsible for ensuring a true scrum process over the course of a project. They hold together the scrum framework, facilitating the process for the organization, product owner and scrum team.

The Fundamentals Of Digital Marketing (04/2020 - Present)

Description

 The Fundamentals of Digital Marketing lays the foundation for understanding how to exploit the different digital marketing tools in order to improve businesses value propositions to customers and improve their overall competitiveness.